Down, Don't you fucking move Each
passenger could be hiding a terrorist and
must be neutralized.
The first hostage taker is found in the
cabin, just one floor up.
Subject down He's swiftly killed, but he
had time to hit a SWAT officer.
5, 6, bridge, to the bridge.
It's a delicate procedure.
There are several passengers to
neutralize.
Hold here, hold here.
Crawl onto me.
Let me see your hands.
Get on the ground, flat on the ground.
Do it now.
Flat on the ground.
Don't reach for nothing.
There remains a crucial step to eliminate
the man threatening the captain.
The first police officer is shot.
The second shoots the terrorist.
Subject down.
One hostage taker remains, but they can't
find his hiding place.
They advance towards the bow.
Hidden on the upper bridge, the final man
is cornered.
Subject down
In the end, the SWAT team takes control of
the boat and averts a major catastrophe.
But two police officers have been shot,
marked in red.
They've been hit.
Fortunately, this particularly dangerous
terrorist attack situation is not a daily
norm.